# JUAN DAVID TABARES ARCE



juandavidarce.co | losmejoresprecios247.com | My blog: juandavidarce.co/blog.html

Calle 12 A N 13-38, Manizales, Colombia Cellphone: 302 271 1608

E-mail: info@juandavidarce.co | juandavidtabaresarce@gmail.com

29 years old (02-20-1988))

#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am a home-based Front-end developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and proficiency in Angular and Bootstrap frameworks. I have spent the last four years coding on a daily basis and learning many aspects of web development since I am a problem solver with a passion for online businesses, UX design and the world wide web.

Juan is always learning and coding and is looking to become an important member of a software and web design company. He is highly motivated and is ready to take today's most difficult challenges web companies have to face.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Colegio Javiera Londoño 🛘 1999

• Diploma de Básica Primaria

### Centro Académico Ased 2005

Bachiller Académico con énfasis en formación empresarial

## Universidad de Caldas | \* 2007-2009

Modern Languages (86 credits)

### 

- Certificate
- Desarrollo Web Complet con HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP y MySQL

# $FreeCodeCamp \square 2017$

- Certificate of acomplishment with highest distinction
- Front-end development program, web Page, Digital / Multimedia and Information Design

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance translator at Upwork (formerly Odesk) 2011 -2013

 Before becoming a web developer I translated many kinds of content from English to Spanish.

### Front-end designer: <a href="https://kueski.com/">https://kueski.com/</a> 2013-2015

• Responsible for web design and maintenance.

#### Freelance Front-end designer: http://juandavidarce.co/ 2013- Present

• I develop websites to customers in a wide range of platforms.

# Front-end designer: <a href="https://www.dukascopy.com/">https://www.dukascopy.com/</a> 2013- 2015

• I worked with a talented team maintaining dukascopy website.

#### Front-end designer: <a href="http://losmejoresprecios247.com/">http://losmejoresprecios247.com/</a> 2017 -Present

• I designed and manage an amazon affiliate website

#### **SKILLS**

- ENGLISH
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, JSON, jQuery, Wordpress, Angular, Bootstrap, SQL, Github, Linux, DNS, WAMP.
- SEO, Google Adwords, Google Analytics.

#### **LEARNING**

• React

#### SOCIAL LINKS

- Web page: <a href="http://juandavidarce.co">http://juandavidarce.co</a>
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/juandavid.tabaresarce
- Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/juan-david-arce-web-developer/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/juan-david-arce-web-developer/</a>
- Codepen: <a href="https://codepen.io/juandata/">https://codepen.io/juandata/</a>
- GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/juandata">https://github.com/juandata</a>
- Google+: <a href="https://plus.google.com/108728558844448484790">https://plus.google.com/108728558844448484790</a>
- Skype: juantabaresarce
- FreeCodeCamp Profile

## PROJECT SAMPLES

- Simon Game: https://codepen.io/juandata/full/mpBmeP/
- Tic Tac Toe Game: https://codepen.io/juandata/pen/wpJbXb
- Calculator: https://codepen.io/juandata/full/vpyoNm/
- Bootstrap Portfolio: https://codepen.io/juandata/full/OOKENJ/
- Wikkipedia Viewer: https://codepen.io/juandata/full/NXWqvq/
- Twitch Tv Api: https://codepen.io/juandata/pen/vpYwjQ

### **REFERENCES**

Available on request.